#### Contact

cinder\_bear@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/stephanie-schrag-2a1128b0 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Leadership Nursing

Healthcare

# Stephanie Schrag

Registered Nurse Supervisor III at Colorado Department of Corrections

Aurora, Colorado

### Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in psychiatric nursing, ICU, ER, medical surgical units, management, virtual clinic nursing, the security and investigations industry. Skilled in Budgeting, Customer Service, Coaching, Business Process Improvement, and Efficiency Implementation as well as the medical field. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse from Montana State University-Billings.

### Experience

Aya Healthcare
Travel Registered Nurse
October 2019 - Present (10 months)

Highlands Behavioral Health System (UHS) Registered Nurse August 2017 - Present (3 years) Littleton, Colorado

Highlands Behavioral Health Systems - UHS Registered Nurse August 2017 - Present (3 years) Highlands Ranch, Colorado

Colorado Department of Corrections
Nurse Supervisor III
October 2018 - October 2019 (1 year 1 month)
Denver

The GEO Group, Inc.
Registered Nurse
February 2017 - September 2017 (8 months)

Aurora, Colorado

Carenet Healthcare Services
Clinical Services Nurse Manager
November 2012 - February 2017 (4 years 4 months)

## Education

Montana State University-Billings
Bachelor's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2005)